# DIVYANSHU KORAT

### FLUTTER DEVELOPER



+91-82389 35855



korat750@gmail.com



Surat, Gujarat, India



https://dk024-dev.github.io./



Divyanshu Korat

### PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional Mobile developer with four years of experience. Mobile app alchemist, transforming ideas into intuitive and engaging experiences. Storyteller with a knack for translating user needs into beautiful and functional apps. Full-stack developer mastering both front-end and back-end development, ensuring seamless app performance.

### SKILLS

- Hybrid Application
- Application Design
- Flutter Development
- Front End
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

## EDUCATION

## DIPLOMA INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Bhagwan Mahavir University

2013 - 2016

## BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Charotar University of Science and Technolgy

2016 - 2019

### EXPERIENCE

#### **FLUTTER DEVELOPER**

Provab Technosoft

2023 - 2024

- Accomplishment/Responsibility/Task
- Analyzed and Improved code stability
- · Mentored and empowered a team of junior developers

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (MOBILE)**

Dev Information Technology Limited

2021 - 2023

- Estimated Product/Modules
- Maintained project resources
- Client communication
- Appreciated: Software Developer(Mobile) Software Developer(Flutter)

### FLUTTER ASSOCIATE DEVELOPER

IBL Infotech

2019 - 2021

- Managed the structure of the code
- Participated in development life-cycle
- Investigated technologies to make development faster
- Appreciated: Flutter Associate Developer Flutter Developer Flutter Trainee

## LANGUAGE

English

• Hindi -

Gujarati

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency